# Bishwajeet Kumar

bishwajeetkoo3@gmail.com 8847606243 Jalandhar jalandhar, punjab

#### **Summary**

Skilled Full Stack developer and a team leader with diverse experience utilizing PHP tools for client-server environments and fluid understanding of many programming languages including JavaScript, XML, and HTML. Worked with the team of GUI and other developers to maintain and improve company projects.

#### **Experience**

### **Full Stack Developer**

TheCodeWork • Silchar, Assam

05/2021 - Present

- · Project lead.
- Issues tracking & completing sprints on jira.
- Co-ordinating with team members & clients on slack to keep the inline development of product & delivery.
- Working on multiple projects at a time.

# **Software Engineer**

Doutedesk • Gurgaon, Haryana

08/2020 - 05/2021

- · Project Lead.
- Development of entire web project & Rest Api for mobile app.
- Integration of third party services.
- Testing, Deployment & Monotiring the product.

## **Laravel Developer**

The Knowledge Accademy • Jalandhar, Punjab

02/2020 - 07/2020

- Helping freshers to get familiar with the framework & existing project.
- Worked on multiple projects.

#### **PHP Developer**

My Ancillary Pvt Ltd. • Kapurthala, Punjab

09/2019 - 03/2020

 Built entire multi-vendor event management system, ERP software & E-Commerce Courier web application.

#### **Skills**

- PHP
- CodeIgniter
- Javascript
- Vue js
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- AWS

- Laravel
- Mysql
- JQuery
- · Tailwind
- HTML
- Git
- Jira

#### **Education**

# **Computer Science & Engineering** Lovely Professional University • Jalandhar, Punjab 06/2020 • Graduated B.Tech in CSE with 7.8 CGPA. 10+2 (Science) National Infotech Higher Secondary School 05/2016 • Completed 10+2 with 66.9% **SLC** Saint Johns Secondary School • Birgunj, Parsa 07/2014 • Completed SLC with 78.2% Languages Hindi • English Github github.com/github-bishwajeet Linkedin

# Portfolio

github-bishwajeet.github.io/portfolio

linkedin.com/in/bishwajeet-kumar-2b044a14a